

BAJJOUK MOUAD Software Developer

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mouadbajjouk/



https://github.com/mouadbajjouk



mouad.baj@gmail.com



https://mouadbajjouk.github.io/portfolio/



+60 14 235 7506

I am Mouad Bajjouk, a master holder in software engineering and self-taught developer since 2017. Experienced desktop, web application, and game development using the latest technologies - Specialized in C#, ASP.NET Core 3.1, SQL Server, MySQL, and Unity game engine.

I am very ambitious to learn new technologies, improve my skills, and gain new experience with the leading-egde technologies.



Education

Master's Degree in Software Engineering

Asia Pacific University (APU) Since November 2019

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science and Applied Mathematics

Ibn Tofail University 09/2016 - 07/2019



Languages

Arabic: Native

French: Proficient

English: Fluent



Work Experience

Web Application Developer

Suplus (Self-employed) 09/2019 - Present

• Creating management systems using ASP.NET Core 3.1 framework and Microsoft SQL server.

Game Developer

Dreamers Studios (Self-employed) 04/2018 - 09/2019

• Desiging and developing hyper-casual games using Unity and C#.



Skills























